[upbeat music]
- All right, everybody, have a good show.
- 好了，各位，演出顺利。
In four, three, two...
四，三，二...
[dramatic music]
You're watching "The Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown"
您正在观看《Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown》
with our number one morning announcements team
由我们排名第一的早间公告团队
and Shelly with the action-cam lowdown.
以及Shelly带来的动作摄像机低角度报道。
It's "Lowdown" time! [buffalo stampede sound]
现在是“低角度报道”时间！
- Good morning, Buffaloes. She's Mae.
- 早上好，水牛们。她是Mae。
- And she's Dawn. - And we're kicking your day off
- 她是Dawn。 - 我们将为您的一天拉开序幕
with all you need to know to be an in-the-know Buffalo.
提供所有你需要知道的信息，让你成为消息灵通的Buffalo。
- Hey, Dawn, don't be nervous
- 嘿，Dawn，别紧张
if you happen to see your parents around school.
如果你在学校里碰巧看到你的父母。
They're just here helping clean up
他们只是来帮忙打扫的
as part of the school's Parents Pitch In program.
作为学校“家长参与”计划的一部分。
- That's good to know, Mae.
- 这很好，Mae。
I thought I was gonna be in a trash heap of trouble.
我还以为我会陷入一堆麻烦中呢。
- [laughs] Good one, Dawn.
- [笑] 说得不错，Dawn。
- Thanks, Mae.
- 谢谢，Mae。
Oh, Mae, I'm super excited
哦，Mae，我超级兴奋
about the seventh grade dance next Saturday.
关于下周六的七年级舞会，
Are tickets still available at the school store for $5?
学校商店还有5美元的票吗？
- They sure are, Dawn.
- 当然有，Dawn。
Now let's go to Dicky Harper
现在让我们去找Dicky Harper
to get the lowdown on the Haps in the Halls.
来了解一下校园里的动态。
Dicky?
Dicky？
- Nice book bag. What do you keep in there?
- 书包不错。你里面装了什么？
- Dicky? - Yeah?
- Dicky？ - 嗯？
- Dicky, you're on.
- Dicky，轮到你了。
- Oh. [whispers] I'll call you.
- 哦。[低声] 我会给你打电话。
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
So, with the big dance coming up,
所以，随着大型舞会的临近，
this year's hot trend is elaborate dance proposals,
今年的热门趋势是精心策划的舞蹈求婚，
or what the kids are calling "dance-posals."
或者孩子们称之为“舞蹈求婚”。
Oh, as you can see, one just happened.
哦，正如你所见，刚刚就发生了一个。
Here come the janitors now to clean up the mess.
现在清洁工会来清理这个烂摊子。
Hello, people who look like sadder versions of my parents.
你好，看起来像是我父母悲伤版本的人们。
What's the old people's take on dance-posals?
老一辈人对舞蹈求婚有什么看法？
- Oh, I think they're sweet.
- 哦，我觉得它们很甜蜜。
- Thanks. I don't get it.
- 谢谢。我不太理解。
Back in my day, you just walked up to a girl,
在我们那个年代，你只需要走到一个女孩面前，
barely looked her in the eye, and just asked.
几乎不直视她的眼睛，然后就直接问。
- Well, it might've been nicer
- 嗯，如果你能多花点心思，
if you'd made a little more of an effort.
可能会更好。
- Well, I got the answer from you I wanted,
- 不过，我得到了我想要的答案，
without littering.
而且没有乱扔垃圾。
Back to you, Dicky.
回到你那里，Dicky。
- Thanks. Oh, you missed a spot.
- 谢谢。哦，你漏了一个地方。
Now to Nicky with the Lowdown on Lunch.
现在转到Nicky，带来午餐的最新消息。
- Thanks, Dicky. Today's menu:
- 谢谢，Dicky。今天的菜单是：
meatloaf with mashed potatoes and gravy.
肉末土豆泥配肉汁。
Now, this is a heavy dish,
现在，这是一道比较油腻的菜，
so rather than pairing with a fuller-bodied whole milk,
所以与其搭配全脂牛奶，
I suggest going with a well-chilled skim.
我建议选择冰镇的脱脂牛奶。
But, as always, my recommendation is
但一如既往，我的建议是
pack you own lunch.
自己带午餐。
Now Avery with the birthdays.
现在轮到Avery报道生日了。
- Happy birthday to Gerald Fitzpatrick.
- 祝Gerald Fitzpatrick生日快乐。
[party horn blows]
[派对号角响起]
And Wendy Baxter,
还有Wendy Baxter，
who didn't invite me to her party.
她没有邀请我去她的派对。
But whatevs. I heard it was totally lame and so weird.
但无所谓。我听说那派对超级无聊而且很奇怪。
Dawn?
Dawn？
- Okay.
- 好的。
Well, now it's time to get really low down
现在，是时候进入大家早上最喜欢的部分了：
on everyone's favorite part of the morning:
[一起] The Shelly-Cam。
[together] The Shelly-Cam.
[学生们叽叽喳喳]
[students chattering]
- 谢谢，Shelly。
- Thanks, Shelly.
那真是一个惊人的壮举。
That was an amazing feat.
好了，今天的节目就到这里。这是
Well, that's all for today. This has been "The Edgewood..."
好了，今天就到这里。这是“The Edgewood...”
[together] "Buffa-lowdown"!
[一起] “Buffa-lowdown”！
[buffalo stampede sound]
[水牛群奔腾声]
- Cut! That's a wrap.
- 停！结束。
Nice work, people.
干得好，各位。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
Oh, I just love that Shelly-Cam.
哦，我太喜欢那个Shelly-Cam了。
Maybe cut to her twice tomorrow. - Got it. Cut Nicky.
也许明天给她两次镜头。 - 明白了。剪掉Nicky。
- I didn't say that. - You didn't have to.
- 我没那么说。 - 你不必说。
- Anyway, as your substitute A/V teacher,
- 无论如何，作为你们的代课音视频老师，
I am very happy with how your project is going.
我对你们项目进展的情况非常满意。
Keep it up, and you'll be more than just the morning team.
继续保持，你们将不仅仅是早间团队。
You'll be the A-team,
你们将成为A队，
as in your grade in this class will be an A.
就像你们在这门课上的成绩将是A一样。
- Yes! - Sweet!
太好了！
- My first non-gym-class A!
太棒了！
- And before you go, everyone, as your A-team leader,
我的第一个非体育课的A！
I'd like to make just one teeny tiny little tweak.
在你们离开之前，作为A队的领导者，
Mae, you're fired!
我想做一个小小的调整。
[together] Fired?
梅，你被解雇了！
- You're out as co-host, and Avery is in!
你不再是联合主持人了，Avery接替你！
[together] Avery?
Avery？
- Avery?
Avery.
Avery。
[upbeat music]
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
♪ ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪ ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ One, two ♪ ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
- ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪ - ♪ Hey! ♪
♪ 一，二，三，四！ ♪ ♪ 嘿！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪
- Ricky, how could you fire Mae?
Ricky，你怎么能解雇Mae？
- You guys should really stop dwelling on the past.
你们真的应该停止纠结过去。
- It was three minutes ago!
那只是三分钟前的事！
- I'm sure Mae's already gotten over it.
我敢肯定Mae已经释怀了。
- Nope.
没有。
- Look, Mae. Don't think of it as being fired.
听着，Mae。不要把它看作是被解雇。
Think of it as a promotion.
把它看作是一次晋升。
- How is losing my job a promotion?
失去工作怎么算是晋升呢？
- I didn't say it was a promotion.
- 我没说这是晋升。
I said "think of it as a promotion."
我是说“把它当作晋升来看待”。
Listen, you're not without some talent,
听着，你并非完全没有才华，
so I'll tell you what I'm gonna do for you:
所以我会告诉你我为你准备的东西：
birthdays!
生日派对！
You're gonna crush it. [party horn blows]
你一定会大放异彩的。[派对号角响起]
- Yes, I am.
- 是的，我会的。
- Told you!
- 我告诉过你了！
- But what about our grade?
- 那我们的评分怎么办？
Mae is clearly a better co-host than Avery.
显然，Mae比Avery更适合做联合主持人。
- That's my call, Dawn. And I make smart decisions.
- 那是我的决定，Dawn。我做出的都是明智的选择。
That's why I'm Team Leader.
这就是为什么我是团队领导。
- Come on, Ricky. Mae and I are perfect together.
- 来吧，Ricky。Mae和我在一起简直是完美搭档。
- How about this, Dawn? Tomorrow before the show,
- 这样如何，Dawn？明天节目开始前，
we'll have a special rehearsal for you and Avery,
我们会为你和Avery安排一场特别的彩排，
and you'll see how well the new pairing works.
你会看到新的组合效果有多好。
Trust me. It'll be music to your ears.
相信我。那将会是悦耳动听的。
- The awards ceremony will be held on the football "filled."
- 颁奖典礼将在足球“满员”举行。
- Um, I think you mean football field.
- 呃，我想你的意思是足球场。
- That's what I said: football filled.
- 我就是这么说的：足球满员。
- Field.
球场。
- Filled.
填满的。
- Fie-eld.
球-场。
- Filled.
填满的。
- Are you trying to mess with me?
你是不是在耍我？
- Love that witty banter. You two are so good together.
喜欢这种机智的斗嘴。你们俩在一起真是太好了。
- How is this better than me?
这怎么比我好？
- It's not. It's a train wreck.
并不好。这是一场灾难。
- I'd rather watch a real train wreck.
我宁愿看一场真正的火车事故。
- I've seen one. And this is much worse.
我见过一次。这个更糟糕。
- That's a wrap on rehearsal.
- 排练结束。
We go live in one minute.
我们一分钟后直播。
Take your places. Let's go, people.
各就各位。大家动起来。
Polish her shell.
打磨她的外壳。
- Ricky, we need to talk.
- 里基，我们需要谈谈。
- We do. I didn't want to say this in front of Avery,
- 是的，我本来不想当着艾弗里的面说，
but that was terrible.
但那真是糟糕透了。
- Thank you. I knew you could see how bad she was.
- 谢谢你。我就知道你能看出她有多差劲。
- I was talking about you. You stunk on ice.
- 我是在说你。你简直糟透了。
- Me? Didn't you hear her?
- 我？你没听她说的吗？
- All I heard was a co-host with charisma.
我只听到一个充满魅力的联合主持人。
You could learn from her.
你可以向她学习。
20 seconds. Take your places.
20秒。各就各位。
- Fine. Since I stink on ice,
好吧。既然我在冰上表现糟糕，
how about you co-host,
不如你来当联合主持人，
and I'll be the producer?
我来当制片人？
- Ha! Give those back!
哈！把那些还给我！
- Too late. We go live in three, two...
太迟了。我们三秒后直播，二……
[buffalo stampede sounds]
[水牛群奔腾声]
- Welcome to Friday's "Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown."
欢迎来到周五的“Edgewood水牛快讯”。
I'm Avery, and this is--
我是Avery，这是——
why are you staring at me?
你为什么盯着我看？
- I'm Rick--[hiccups]
我是Rick——[打嗝]
I'm Rick--[hiccups] I'm--[hiccups]
我是Rick——[打嗝] 我是——[打嗝]
Go to Dick--[hiccups]--y.
去Dick——[打嗝]——y。
- Weird.
奇怪。
- Just go to Dicky.
直接去Dicky。
- [exhales, inhales]
[呼气，吸气]
Nice.
不错。
- Dude!
伙计！
- Oh. Right.
哦，对。
Word in the hall is the water in this drinking fountain tastes
传闻说这个饮水机的水喝起来
like belly button sweat.
像肚脐眼里的汗。
- Need water!
需要水！
- But this thirsty little fella doesn't seem to mind.
但这口渴的小家伙似乎并不介意。
♪ ♪
♪
[all laughing]
（大家都在笑）
- Hey, what happened to you?
嘿，你怎么了？
- Yeah. How did you drink so much water?
是啊，你怎么喝了这么多水？
Are you part fish or something?
你该不会是半条鱼吧？
Are we all part fish?
我们都是鱼变的吗？
Okay, I'm getting excited about this fish thing.
好吧，我对这个鱼的话题有点兴奋了。
- I thought we were supposed to be the A-team, Ricky.
- 我还以为我们是A队呢，Ricky。
- And whatever you did out there is not going to get us an A.
- 你在外面做的那些事可不会让我们得A。
- I don't know what happened. I just--
- 我不知道发生了什么。我只是——
- Are you okay?
- 你还好吗？
Why did you start acting so weird?
你为什么开始表现得这么奇怪？
- I--[hiccups]
- 我——[打嗝]
I--[hiccups]--water!
我——[打嗝]——水！
- Weird.
- 奇怪。
- That's strange.
那很奇怪。
Every time Ricky's around Avery, he gets all...
每次Ricky在Avery附近，他就变得...
I--[hiccups]-- I--[hiccups]
我——[打嗝]——我——[打嗝]
- It all makes sense!
这一切都说得通了！
Replacing Mae with Avery, refusing to criticize Avery,
用Avery取代Mae，拒绝批评Avery，
freaking out whenever Avery's around--
每当Avery在附近就紧张——
it's so obvious!
太明显了！
- Yeah. Avery's turning him into a fish!
是啊。Avery把他变成了鱼！
- No, Dicky. Ricky has a crush on Avery.
不，Dicky。Ricky对Avery有好感。
- I don't know. This fish thing makes more sense.
我不知道。这个鱼的事情更有道理。
- ♪ Oh-oh, hey, oh-oh-oh-oh-oh ♪
哦-哦，嘿，哦-哦-哦-哦-哦
- So, Ricky, we have a theory about why you choked up.
那么，Ricky，我们有个理论解释你为什么会紧张。
- I don't like Avery!
我不喜欢Avery！
- I also have a theory.
我也有个理论。
- He is not a fish.
他不是一条鱼。
You have a crush on Avery, don't you, Ricky?
你对Avery有意思，对吧，Ricky？
- Uh, no! I'm a fish!
呃，不是！我是一条鱼！
- You fired me for a crush?
你因为暗恋她就把我解雇了？
- Yeah. We're all going to get a terrible grade because of her.
是的。我们都会因为她而得个糟糕的成绩。
- You need to put Avery back on birthdays.
你需要让Avery重新负责生日活动。
- Why? She's perfect as co-host.
为什么？她作为联合主持人非常完美。
She's so sweet and kind and wonderful,
她那么甜美、善良、美好，
and her voice is like an angel's song.
她的声音就像天使的歌声。
- An angel's song?
天使的歌声？
Oh, this boy is crushin' hard.
哦，这男孩陷得可深了。
- I don't get it. What was your plan after you gave her the job?
我不明白。你给她这份工作后有什么计划？
- I don't know.
我不知道。
I'd be the producer. She'd be the co-host.
我会是制片人。她会是联合主持人。
We'd get an A. And then we'd get married.
我们能得A。然后我们会结婚。
- Married? You can't even talk to her.
结婚？你甚至都不敢跟她说话。
- I could before Dawn took my headset and clipboard.
- 在Dawn拿走我的耳机和夹纸板之前，我还可以。
- Hey.
- 嘿。
- [hiccups]
- [打嗝]
I need my headset and clipboard!
我需要我的耳机和夹纸板！
- Look. We all want a good grade,
- 听着。我们都想要个好成绩，
but we're not just the A-team.
但我们不仅仅是A队。
We're also Team Harper.
我们也是Harper团队。
And I think I know a way we can both get our A,
我想我知道一个方法，我们都能得到我们的A，
as in our grade and Avery.
也就是我们的成绩和Avery。
- Thanks. So, which one of you wants to be Avery's co-host?
- 谢谢。那么，你们谁想成为Avery的联合主持人？
- I think I speak for both of us when I say "nuh-uh."
- 我想我代表我们俩说一句：“不不不。”
- We just have to get you comfortable talking to Avery.
- 我们只需要让你习惯和Avery交谈。
And I think I know how.
而且我想我知道怎么做。
- Welcome to "The Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown."
- 欢迎来到“Edgewood低语者”。
I'm Ricky.
我是Ricky。
- [as Avery] Hi, Ricky. It's me, Avery.
- [模仿Avery] 嗨，Ricky。是我，Avery。
- This isn't helping. You sound nothing like her.
- 这没用。你一点儿也不像她。
- Please. [as Avery] That was totes Avery.
- 拜托。[模仿Avery] 那绝对是Avery。
- Let me try.
- 让我试试。
[As Avery] Something's fishy, Ricky,
[模仿Avery] 有点不对劲，Ricky，
and I think it's you.
我觉得是你。
- No. Avery's more like...
- 不，Avery更像是...
[in high-pitched voice] Hi. I'm Avery.
[用高音调的声音] 嗨，我是Avery。
- You sound like Mom.
- 你听起来像妈妈。
- No, I don't. Mom's more like...
- 不，我不像。妈妈更像是...
[in high-pitched voice] Hi. I'm Mom.
[用高音调的声音] 嗨，我是妈妈。
- No, she's not. Mom is like--
- 不，她不是。妈妈的声音像是——
- It doesn't matter what Mom sounds like!
- 妈妈的声音是什么样并不重要！
I like Avery! I don't like Mom!
我喜欢Avery！我不喜欢妈妈！
- What did I just hear? - Nothing! Love you!
- 我刚刚听到了什么？ - 什么都没有！爱你！
This isn't helping. None of you sound like Avery.
这没用。你们谁都不像Avery。
- How about me?
- 那我呢？
- Why are you staring at me?
- 你为什么盯着我？
- [hiccups]
- [打嗝]
- Okay, now we're onto something.
- 好了，现在有点进展了。
Let's go from the top.
我们从头再来。
- Why are you staring at me?
- 你为什么盯着我？
- Welcome to-- - Why are you staring at me?
- 欢迎来到-- 你为什么盯着我？
- [hiccups] Welcome to "The Edge--"
- [打嗝] 欢迎来到“The Edge--”
- Why are you staring at me? - [hiccups]
- 你为什么盯着我？ - [打嗝]
- [as Avery] You can do this, Ricky!
你可以做到的，Ricky！
- Focus! - Conquer your fear!
集中注意力！克服你的恐惧！
- Quiet, Mom! Welcome to "The Edgewood Buffa--"
安静，妈妈！欢迎来到“Edgewood Buffa--”
- Why are you staring at me?
你为什么盯着我看？
- I'm staring at you because I have a crush on you!
我盯着你是因为我喜欢你！
Welcome to "The Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown."
欢迎来到“Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown”。
Marry me.
嫁给我。
- Okay. At least you can talk to her,
好吧。至少你能和她说话，
but you might want to pace yourself.
但你可能需要控制一下自己的节奏。
- Yeah.
是的。
[upbeat music]
- You're ready. - I'm going in.
- 你准备好了。 - 我要进去了。
- And remember: try not to propose.
- 记住：尽量不要求婚。
- Hey, Ricky.
- 嘿，Ricky。
- Hey, Avery.
- 嘿，Avery。
I didn't--[hiccups]-- it worked!
我没——[打嗝]——成功了！
- You did great.
- 你做得很好。
[gasps] Look who's waving at you.
[吸气声] 看谁在向你挥手。
- Oh, this is great. What's my next move?
- 哦，这太棒了。我下一步该做什么？
- Next move?
- 下一步？
We go on the show. We get an A. Everybody happy.
我们上节目。我们得个A。大家都开心。
- No! With Avery.
不行！要和Avery一起。
How do I take this to the next level?
我怎么把这个提升到下一个层次？
[dramatic music]
[戏剧性音乐]
- Hey, girl. You'll always be my co-host,
嘿，女孩。你永远都是我的搭档，
so would you like to...
所以你愿意...
go to the dance with me?
和我一起去跳舞吗？
- I knew you were going to do this, so...
我就知道你会这么做，所以...
yes!
是的！
- Aww! - I know.
哎呀！我知道。
Now I have to clean this up, too.
现在我也得清理这个了。
- That's how you take it to the next level:
这就是你把它提升到下一个层次的方式：
a dance-posal.
一个舞会姿势。
And you should do it on the show!
你应该在节目上做这个！
- Really? That seems like a big move.
真的吗？那看起来是个大动作。
- Avery will love it.
艾弗里会喜欢的。
- Tarian will love it.
塔里安会喜欢的。
- Trust the team.
相信团队。
- Well, you've been right so far.
嗯，到目前为止你都是对的。
Uh-oh. She's walking over here.
哎呀。她正朝这边走来。
- Where's the bathroom?
洗手间在哪儿？
- We have two. I'd go to the one on the second floor.
我们有两个。我建议去二楼的那一个。
That's the one with the good paper towels.
那个有好的纸巾。
- Thanks.
谢谢。
- I am on fire!
我状态火热！
[leaf blower whirring] - Oh! Whoa!
哦！哇！
♪ ♪
♪
- Black background. Brown background.
黑色背景。棕色背景。
- Hey, Ricky. How's it going?
嘿，Ricky。最近怎么样？
- Great. I got the last onion bagel this morning,
很好。今天早上我拿到了最后一个洋葱百吉饼，
and Mom pressed my favorite slacks!
还让妈妈熨了我最喜欢的裤子！
- So, you ready for your epic dance-posal?
那么，准备好你的舞蹈求婚了吗？
- Yep. I typed it into the teleprompter,
是的，我把它输入到提词器里了，
just in case I forget the words or get nervous.
以防万一我忘记歌词或者紧张。
- There's absolutely no reason to get nervous.
完全没有理由紧张。
- I don't want to make you guys nervous,
我不想让你们紧张，
but Principal Tarian just told me
但塔里安校长刚刚告诉我，
if we have another show like Friday's,
如果我们再有一场像周五那样的表演，
we can forget about being his A-team.
我们就可以忘记成为他的A队了。
- That makes me nervous.
这让我有点紧张。
- Don't worry. We got this.
- 别担心，我们能搞定。
Now, to ensure our A, you go warm up some more.
现在，为了确保我们的A，你去再热身一下。
- Box of biscuits.
- 一盒饼干。
- And to ensure his Avery,
- 为了确保他的Avery，
I'm gonna go lay down some dance-posal groundwork.
我要去打一些舞蹈姿势的基础。
Hey, Avery. I was wondering:
嘿，Avery，我在想：
are you planning on going to the dance with anyone special?
你打算和谁一起去跳舞吗？
- Why? - No reason.
- 为什么？ - 没什么。
So, anybody?
那么，有人选吗？
- I don't know.
- 我不知道。
- It sounds like you know.
- 听起来你心里有数。
- Well, there's this guy I kind of hope asks me.
- 嗯，有个男生我希望他能邀请我。
- And he is? - Your brother.
- 他是谁？ - 你哥哥。
- Got three of 'em.
- 我有三个哥哥。
- He's on "The Buffa-Lowdown."
- 他在“The Buffa-Lowdown”节目里。
- We all are.
- 我们都在。
- His name rhymes with "icky."
- 他的名字和“icky”押韵。
- Keep going.
- 继续说。
- Like Ricky. - Yes!
- 像Ricky。 - 对！
- It's Nicky.
- 是Nicky。
- [stammering] Nicky?
- [结巴] 尼基？
Uh, are you sure you didn't mean to say Ricky?
呃，你确定不是想说里基吗？
- Ricky? He's sweet,
- 里基？他很可爱，
but he smells like onion bagels,
但他闻起来像洋葱百吉饼，
and his pants are pressed.
而且他的裤子熨得笔挺。
- But what about the smile you gave him yesterday in the cafe?
- 但你昨天在咖啡馆对他笑是怎么回事？
I mean, we all saw it.
我是说，我们都看到了。
- I was smiling at Nicky, behind Ricky.
- 我是在对里基后面的尼基笑。
He was being supes cute.
他当时超级可爱。
- This is supes not good.
- 这超级不好。
[upbeat music]
- Guys, we have a big problem.
伙计们，我们有个大问题。
I just found out that Avery isn't into Ricky.
我刚发现Avery对Ricky没兴趣。
She's into Nicky.
她对Nicky有意思。
- She likes me?
她喜欢我？
I'm flattered, but I just don't see an "us."
我受宠若惊，但我看不出我们有什么可能。
- Not the point.
不是重点。
We need to tell Ricky before he embarrasses himself
我们需要在Ricky自取其辱之前告诉他，
and gets rejected in front of the entire school.
以免他在全校面前被拒绝。
- Whoa! What are you guys doing?
哇！你们在干什么？
We go live in 20 seconds. Get in your positions.
我们20秒后开始直播。各就各位。
- Oh, we just needed to tell Ricky something.
- 哦，我们只是需要告诉Ricky一些事情。
- Is it, "You got a bad grade
- 是关于“你得了个坏成绩
"because you didn't listen to Principal Tarian
“因为你没有听从Tarian校长的建议
and ruined the morning announcements"?
还毁了早间公告”吗？
- No.
- 不是。
- I didn't think so. Now take your places.
- 我就知道。现在各就各位。
- We're just gonna need to figure out a way
- 我们只需要想办法
to get through to him on air.
在直播中让他明白。
[exciting music plays] - We're live in three, two...
[激动人心的音乐播放] - 我们三秒后直播，二秒...
♪ ♪
♪
- Good morning.
- 早上好。
Welcome to "The Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown."
欢迎来到《Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown》。
She's Avery.
她是Avery。
- And I'm Avery.
- 我是Avery。
- You know, Avery, I have a feeling
- 你知道吗，Avery，我有种感觉
today's show is going to be
今天的节目将会是
the most memorable in history.
历史上最难忘的一次。
And now it's time for today's Buffa-birthdays.
现在是今天的Buffa生日时间。
Mae?
Mae？
- Thanks, Ricky. Big Buffalo birthday wishes to...
谢谢，Ricky。向...送上大水牛的生日祝福：
Siena Meyer and Curtis Nelson.
Siena Meyer和Curtis Nelson。
Now back to Rick--
现在回到Rick--
Listen to these, Ricky:
听听这些，Ricky：
A big happy birthday to Hugh Shuden-Tasker.
祝Hugh Shuden-Tasker生日快乐。
Hear that?
听到了吗？
Hugh Shuden-Tasker.
Hugh Shuden-Tasker。
And lastly,
最后，
Ixnay Ontha Antsday.
Ixnay Ontha Antsday。
Ricky?
Ricky？
- Uh, well, I don't know you, Ixnay,
- 呃，好吧，我不认识你，Ixnay，
but I'd like to wish you and all the international students
但我想要向你和所有国际学生
a special Edgewood welcome to America.
特别地欢迎来到美国，Edgewood式的。
- Now let's get the Haps in the Halls.
- 现在让我们在走廊里热闹起来。
Dicky?
Dicky？
- Thanks, Avery.
- 谢谢，Avery。
Dance-posals are bigger than ever.
舞蹈提案比以往任何时候都更受欢迎。
Wait.
等等。
Dance-posals are over.
舞蹈提案已经结束了。
Nobody's doing them anymore,
现在没人再做这些了，
so if you're thinking about doing one,
所以，如果你在考虑这样做，
forget it!
忘了吧！
- Uh, what do you think, Avery?
- 呃，你怎么看，Avery？
Are dance-posals still cool?
舞蹈求婚还酷吗？
- I guess. - You hear that, people?
- 我想是的。
She guesses.
- 你们听到了吗，人们？
- Ugh!
她只是猜测。
- He's just not getting it.
- 唉！
- Then it's time to get him out of here.
- 他就是不明白。
Cut to the Shelly-Cam.
- 那么是时候让他离开这里了。
- Does Shelly love Daddy?
Shelly爱爸爸吗？
Daddy loves Shelly.
爸爸爱Shelly。
Why's that little red light on?
为什么那个小红灯亮着？
Hey, guys, why is this red light on?
嘿，伙计们，这个红灯为什么亮着？
- Can I have a word with you?
我能和你谈一下吗？
- Yeah, sure. Excuse me--
当然可以，不好意思——
Wait! I had a question for Avery!
等等！我有个问题要问Avery！
What did you want to tell me?
你想告诉我什么？
- Nicky, I need you to fill in for Ricky.
Nicky，我需要你代替Ricky上场。
- What? I can't go up there with Avery.
什么？我不能和Avery一起上去。
She likes me. It's a very awkward situation.
她喜欢我。这情况很尴尬。
- Just read the teleprompter and wrap it up
- 只要照着提词器读，快点结束
so he can't do his dance-posal.
这样他就没法做他的舞蹈动作了。
Back to camera one!
回到一号摄像机！
- And that's "The Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown."
- 这就是《艾奇伍德低音速递》。
Uh, just one thing before we go.
呃，在我们结束前还有一件事。
Avery, would you like to go to the dance with me?
艾弗里，你愿意和我一起去跳舞吗？
[gasps] [both gasp]
[倒吸气] [两人同时倒吸气]
- [gasps]
- [倒吸气]
- Why did I read that thing?
- 我为什么要读那东西？
- Wrap it up!
- 结束吧！
- Uh, cue balloons and band.
- 呃，准备气球和乐队。
Why do I keep reading that thing?
为什么我总是读那东西？
[band playing]
[乐队演奏]
♪ ♪
- Stop!
- 停！
That's my music and balloons!
那是我的音乐和气球！
- What's happening?
- 发生了什么？
Ooh, balloons.
哦，气球。
- Scared of balloons! I'm out.
- 害怕气球！我走了。
- Don't worry. I got this.
别担心，我来搞定。
[band plays heroic music]
[乐队演奏英雄音乐]
- Stop!
停！
You! You betrayed me.
你！你背叛了我。
How could you?
你怎么能这样？
[band plays tense music]
[乐队演奏紧张音乐]
- I was just reading the teleprompter
我只是照着提词器读，就像道恩告诉我的那样。
like Dawn told me to.
你！你背叛了我。
- You! You betrayed me.
你怎么能这样？
How could you?
[乐队演奏紧张音乐]
[band plays tense music]
[乐队演奏紧张的音乐]
- What are you talking about?
- 你在说什么？
- Yeah. What are you talking about?
- 是啊，你在说什么？
- I was going to ask you to the dance,
- 我本来想邀请你去舞会的，
but Dawn set me up.
但Dawn设计了我。
This was all an elaborate plan to embarrass me.
这一切都是一个精心策划的计划，为了让我难堪。
- Uh, no, it wasn't. We were all just trying to help you.
- 呃，不是的。我们都是想帮你。
- Yeah, that's true. - She's right.
- 是啊，没错。 - 她说得对。
- Oh, please. You were trying to get back at me
- 哦，拜托。你是想报复我
for replacing Mae with Avery to get Avery to like me.
因为我用Avery替换了Mae，想让Avery喜欢我。
- Wait. I thought I got the co-host spot on my own "mert."
等等，我以为我是凭自己的“mert”得到了联合主持的位置。
- Did--did you say "merit"?
你——你刚才是说“merit”吗？
- Yeah. Mert.
对，mert。
- Oh, my gosh. I hear it now.
哦，天哪，我现在听出来了。
- Come on, Nicky. Let's get out of here.
走吧，Nicky，我们离开这里。
- Uh, actually, Avery,
呃，实际上，Avery，
I was thinking of asking someone else to the dance.
我在考虑邀请别人去跳舞。
[band plays tense music]
（乐队演奏紧张的音乐）
Natlee, would you like to go to the dance with me?
Natlee，你愿意和我一起去跳舞吗？
[drum roll]
（鼓声滚动）
- Actually, I wanted Dooley to ask me.
实际上，我希望Dooley来邀请我。
[band plays tense music]
乐队演奏紧张的音乐
- Me?
我？
Okay. Uh...[clears throat]
好的。呃...[清嗓子]
Natlee,
Natlee，
will you go to the dance with me?
你愿意和我一起去参加舞会吗？
[drum roll]
鼓声响起
- Yes.
是的。
[band plays happy tune]
乐队演奏欢快的曲调
♪ ♪
- Stop that!
停下！
What is going on here?
这里发生了什么？
We're still on the air! And Dawn and Ricky,
我们还在直播！而且Dawn和Ricky，
you have completely lost control of your show.
你们完全失去了对节目的控制。
This isn't the A-team. You're the D-team.
这不是A队。你们是D队。
D for "disappointing," not your grade.
D代表‘令人失望’，不是你们的等级。
You'll probably get a B-minus.
你们可能会得到一个B-。
- We haven't lost control.
我们没有失去控制。
This was all part of an intricately planned dance-posal
这一切都是精心策划的舞蹈提案的一部分
to give people an in-depth look at the phenomenon.
为了让人们深入了解这一现象。
- Uh, yeah, we totally knew what we were doing.
- 呃，是的，我们完全知道自己在做什么。
- Yeah. Congrats, Natlee and Dooley.
- 是的。恭喜Natlee和Dooley。
- You crazy kids.
- 你们这些疯狂的孩子。
- Wow. Now, that's A-plus work.
- 哇。现在，这才是A+的工作。
And I am talking about their grade.
我说的是他们的成绩。
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
- As promised, this has been
- 如承诺的，这已成为
a very memorable episode of
一段非常难忘的
"The Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown."
"The Edgewood Buffa-Lowdown"节目。
[buffalo stampede sounds]
[野牛群奔声]
Cut! That's a wrap. Whoo!
停！结束。哇！
- Man, that was quick thinking, Ricky.
伙计，那真是机智，瑞奇。
- It's the least I could do after what you all did for me.
这是我最起码能做的，感谢你们为我所做的一切。
I was selfish, but now I realize
我曾经很自私，但现在我意识到
you have to look after your team,
你必须照顾好你的团队，
because they're the most important thing you've got.
因为他们是你最重要的财富。
- Hey, Ricky,
嘿，瑞奇，
thanks for saving our A.
谢谢你救了我们。
Would you like to go to the dance with "may"?
你想和'may'一起去跳舞吗？
- Uh, I think Mae's already going with Miles.
呃，我想梅已经和迈尔斯一起去了。
- No. I meant with "may," not Mae.
不，我是说和“May”，不是Mae。
"May."
“May”。
- Yes. I'd love to.
是的，我很愿意。
Okay, seriously, how did I not hear that before?
好吧，说真的，我之前怎么没听到这个？
- [as Avery] They're just supes cute.
（扮演Avery）他们超级可爱。
- [as Avery] I know!
（扮演Avery）我知道！
[band plays upbeat music]
（乐队演奏欢快的音乐）
- ♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
♪ Na, na, na, na, na, na ♪
[whistling]
（吹口哨）
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
- ♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
- ♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪